<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Memoir</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_shoot_video">Shoot Video</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">About</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Memoir application creates a short movie with two second video clips shot each day of your life. You can then view the movie to recall some of best moments of your life!</string>
    <string name="start_movie">Get Started</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Shoot video</string>
    <string name="title_section2">My Life</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Settings</string>
    <string name="contextual_menu_select">Select</string>
    <string name="contextual_menu_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="startDateLabel">Start Date:</string>
    <string name="endDateLabel">End Date:</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_version">Version 1.0 Copyrights reserved</string>
    
    
    <string name="activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_mt1">Help </string>
    <string name="help_t1">Memoir application creates a short movie with two second video clips shot each day of your life. You can either manually click a video of a memorable event in the day or the application can do it for you. You can then view the movie to recall some of your best moments summarized in a few minutes!</string>
    <string name="help_mt2">Getting started</string>
    <string name="help_t2">1. Take videos each day by clicking on SHOOT VIDEO. The videos are displayed in a list for each date. 
2. You can take multiple videos in a day but only one video per day is selected for your movie. 
3. Press and hold the video thumbnail to select/delete from videos for a day.
4. You can view the complete movie by clicking the play button above list of videos.
5. Each time a video is taken/selected/deleted or start/end dates are changed, the movie is updated with the new selections.
6. Share your movie by clicking the “(share image)” button.</string>
    <string name="help_mt3">How to change Start/End date for movie</string>
    <string name="help_t3">1. Go to Settings.
2. Select “Set Start Date” or “Set End Date” to change dates.
3. Your movie is updated to show videos within selected dates.</string>
    <string name="help_mt4">How to take videos</string>
    <string name="help_t4">1. Start by clicking “SHOOT VIDEO” option.
2. Hold the camera is Landscape mode while shooting.
3. The camera automatically stops recording after 2 seconds.
4. You can review, select or cancel the current video. On selecting, the video is added to list of videos.
	</string>
    <string name="help_mt5">How to Select/Delete videos</string>
    <string name="help_t5">1. Selected video for the day is highlighted in blue in the list of videos. By default, the last video taken for the day is selected.
2. Touch and hold video for options Select/Delete.
3. If a selected video is deleted, the next video is marked selected.
	</string>

    <string name="help_mt6">How to Share videos</string>
    <string name="help_t6">1. Click on Share symbol on top bar to view list of available sharing options.
2. Your movie is exported in .mp4 format and shared.
	</string>

</resources>